<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
	<contents>
		<content>
			<headline><![CDATA[LTS Laboratory Diversification Program]]></headline>
			<paragraph><![CDATA[In 1997, LTS established our Laboratory Diversification Program. To compliment our Nondestructive Testing services we've added other quality services such as Sandblasting, Welding, Mechanical Polishing, and CNC Precision Machining to achieve our goal of total customer satisfaction and to deliver outstanding quality services in a timely manner at a competitive rate.]]></paragraph>
			<paragraph><![CDATA[Many products being inspected utilizing Nondestructive Testing methods also require specific processes after inspections have been completed. Providing multiple quality and accurate services at our facility can help reduce transportation costs and lead times for our customers.]]></paragraph>
			<paragraph><![CDATA[Example: Processes required on Lifting Brackets P/N 122-3204, all of which were accomplished at our facility:
							<ol>
								<li>CNC Precision Machining</li>
								<li>Pre-Clean</li>
								<li>Magnetic Particle Inspection</li>
								<li>Demagnetization</li>
								<li>Post Wash</li>
								<li>Sandblasting</li>
								<li>Visual Inspection</li>
								<li>Rust Inhibitor Application</li>
								<li>Package, Stock and Release.</li>
							</ol>]]></paragraph>
			<paragraph><![CDATA[We would like to work with you to determine your requirements and design our services to meet your specific needs. If you would like a quote or additional information on any of our available services, please <b>call anytime at <nobr>(414) 332-3677</nobr> or <nobr>(800) 337-4884.</nobr></b>]]></paragraph>
			<paragraph><![CDATA[<h3>SOME OF THOSE INDUSTRIES WHICH LTS SERVICES ARE:</h3>
							<ul class="listblack floatLeft margin_0_20_0_0">
								<li>Pharmaceutical Industry</li>
								<li>Food Industry</li>
								<li>Pulp and Paper</li>
								<li>Automotive</li>
							</ul>
							<ul class="listblack floatLeft">
								<li>Casting Industry</li>
								<li>Aerospace</li>
								<li>Department of Transportation</li>
								<li>Refinery Industry</li>
							</ul><br />]]></paragraph>
		</content>
	</contents>